我们得揍扁多少个蠢货
How many of these goons do we have to bap
他们才会长教训
before they get the hint?
是的 他们一直不停地冒出来
Really. They just keep coming.
是时候启动B计划了
Time to switch to plan B.
多纳泰罗
Donatello?
马上就好 李奥
Almost there, Leo.
巴士即将出发 前往任何地方
This bus now leaving for anywhere
反正不是这里
but here!
快走 我们出发
Come on! We're going!
哦 开得真好 多尼
Whoa! Nice driving, Don,
对于一只没驾照的乌龟来说
for a turtle with no license!
嘿 你想要中看还是中用
Hey, you want pretty, or you want effective?
我得告诉你 今天真是诡异的一天
I gotta tell you, this has been one mondo bizarro day.
首先是地下那些金属机器人
First, all those metal robot things underground.
还有那些忍者是怎么回事
And what's with all those ninjas?
纽约除了我们还有别的忍者?
Ninjas in New York City? Besides us?
这太不对劲了
It's just not right.
说到不对劲
Talk about not right.
快来看看这个
Check this out.
让我看看这些钱 宝贝
Show me the money, baby!
喔吼
Whoo-hoo!
这可不是谁捡到就归谁 麦奇
This isn't finders keepers, Mikey.
伙计们 看好这些钱 行吗
Take care of this money, will you, guys?
你看见了吗
Did you see that?
一些开装甲车的小绿人
Some little green men in an armored car
朝我们扔了一大堆钱
just threw a bunch of money at us!
哈 菜鸟
Rookie.
嘿
Hey!
老师 你没事
Sensei, you're all right!
斯普林特! 好哎!
- Splinter! - Yeah!
是的 我也很高兴看到你们
Yes, well, I'm glad to see you, too,
我的孩子们
my sons.
斯普林特老师
Master Splinter,
今天发生了太多事
so much has happened today.
好的 好的
Yes, yes.
稍后有的是时间告诉我
There will be time to tell me all about it later
李奥纳多
Leonardo,
但首先
but first,
我想先带你们回家
I wish to take you all home.
家?
Home?
我们没有家了
We got no home.
那些机器人把我们的家毁了
Those robots trashed our pad.
还记得吗 老师
Remember, Sensei?
别担心
Do not worry.
我想我已经找到了方法
I think I have found a solution
解决我们的住房问题
to our current housing problem.
跟我来 孩子们
Follow me, my sons.
卡哇邦....
Cowabun--
啊
Aah!
这不好笑 拉夫
Not funny, Raph!
哦 当然好笑
Oh, yes, it is.
超赞的滑行
Wicked slide!
无意冒犯 斯普林特老师
No offense, Master Splinter,
但这地方看起来不怎么样
but this place doesn't seem so great.
用心去看 米开朗基罗
Look with your heart, Michelangelo,
而不是用你的眼睛
and not your eyes.
嗯 好吧
Um, okay.
往这边走
And walk this way.
哇
Wow!
这简直太棒了
This is beyond awesome!
我可以把这里改造一下
I could really tune this space up.
这间屋子 归我了
This room here, mine.
你站的那里 也是我的
And where you're standing, also mine.
听着孩子们 改变是好事
You see, my sons, change is good.
我们完全赞同 斯普林特老师
We couldn't agree more, Master Splinter.
很好
Good.
这次换你们几个来打扫吧
So let's see you boys clean up for a change.
这房间太脏了
This chamber is filthy.
唉 老兄
Aw, man.
先生 我...我...
Sir? I--I--
我的手下们
my men,
我们...我们把运钞的装甲车弄丢了
we--we lost the armored car with the money.
但是我们是被袭击了
But we were attacked
被某种空手道青蛙生物之类的袭击
by some sort of karate frog creatures or something.
他们打了我们一个措手不及
They took us by surprise.
那不是我的错
It wasn't my fault.
够了
Enough.
我保证 先生 我不会再让你失望了
I promise, sir, I won't fail you again.
我知道
I know.
你不会再让我失望了 永远
You won't fail me again, ever.
不 先生 求你了
No, sir! Please!